http://www.aerotype.com/privacy

b
Shopping cart is empty.
A to ZAmericanusApplewoodArbordaleBlackstockBootstrapBoxwoodBuckboardCabooseColdsmithCopperjackDerailerDogjawDracenaDracturaDuendeFaveGeoduckGhost TrainGothicusHogwildKeepsakeKhakiKingsheadLeadvilleMeritageObsoleteOctoberfestPacificoPublic WorksReboundRecycleRoughneckSilvertonSluiceboxStay TrueThunderhouseTurbinadoWilhelmschriftZooja
stylesscriptdistressedwood type & metalblackletter / fraktur
packagesHome
Aerotype Corporation Privacy Policy
Aerotype is committed to protecting your privacy. This document sets forth the Aerotype Privacy Policy (the “Privacy Policy”) for this web site, www.aerotype.com (the “Site”). Because we collect two types of user information, General Statistical Information and Personal Identifying Information, we are providing you with this policy to inform you of how we use and, in limited circumstances, disclose such information. If you have objections to the Privacy Policy, you should not access or use this Site.
Collection, Use and Disclosure of General Statistical Information
When you visit our web site we gather certain general information, such as number of hits on our web site, frequency of downloads, and usage statistics with respect to our software products. This information is referred to throughout this policy as "General Statistical Information". We use and store this data only on a collective basis, in summary form. This data helps us to determine how and the extent to which certain parts of our web site and software are used. The stored General Statistical Information does not contain any Personal Identifying Information about you or any of our other users.
Collection and Use of Personal Identifying Information
In addition to collecting General Statistical Information, we may ask you to provide us with certain personal information, such as your name, street address and email address, to enable us to respond to your requests and needs. Information that can reasonably be used to identify you is referred to in this policy as "Personal Identifying Information". For example, if you choose to make a purchase online, or through other means such as a purchase order, we will request Personal Identifying Information necessary for payment, invoicing, and/or shipping. When you provide us Personal Identifying Information in an e-mail, fax or by telephone such as when you request technical and other types of support, we use the information to locate your records and provide you with answers to your questions. In addition, your personal information helps us and selected third parties to keep you posted on products and special offers that you might like to hear about.
Removal from Mailing List or Change of Personal Information
You may have your e-mail address removed from our mailing list by emailing us at 'products@aerotype.com' with the word 'remove' in the subject line. You may also change your Personal Identifying Information in our database by e-mailing us at 'products@aerotype.com'.
Disclosure of Personal Identifying Information
We may disclose your Personal Identifying Information to appropriate third parties to process transactions you initiate, including shipping products to you and invoicing for purchases made. Examples of such third parties are our order processing and fulfillment service providers and credit card processing companies. We may also disclose your Personal Identifying Information to third parties if we are required to do so by law, or if we believe that such action is necessary to:
* Comply with legal processes such as a search warrant, subpoena, or court order;
* Protect our rights and property; or
* Protect against misuse or unauthorized use of our web site and/or Aerotype products.
We never loan, rent or sell your Personal Identifying Information to others.
Cookies
We may set and access cookies on your computer. A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from a Web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. We use cookies in a limited way to track usage on our site. We gather information about site use by our visitors through cookie technology on an anonymous basis and analyze it at an aggregate level only. This enables us to continually improve our website to meet the needs of our users.
In addition, we may use temporary session cookies to track your progress through our order processing system, keeping track of information such as the contents of your shopping cart and address. These session cookies only exist for the duration of your browser session.
Third Party Web Sites
The Aerotype web site may contain links to third-party web sites over which we have no control or responsibility regarding content, privacy policies, or practices. We suggest that you review the privacy policy applicable to any third party site that you visit. This privacy policy applies only to our own web site at www.aerotype.com. Please note that all on-line and telephone credit card orders for Aerotype software products may be processed by a third party.
Web Site Security
Our web site utilizes industry standard security technology to protect the security, integrity, and privacy of Personal Identifying Information from unauthorized third-party access. The Personal Identifying Information resides behind a firewall with access restricted to authorized Aerotype employees and their agents.
Changes to the Aerotype Privacy Policy
Aerotype may amend this policy at any time by posting the amended terms on our web site. All amended terms will be automatically effective without further notice, 10 days after they are first posted.
Licensing Options
Contact Us
a
Copyright © 1995- Aerotype Corporation. All Rights Reserved. Terms of Service  Privacy Policy
